Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Conferences, Series IX
  - Twenty-ninth Annual Conference - South Hamilton, MA
    - Proceedings, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 882)
    - Conference Material, 1975 (Box 74, Folder 883)
  - Thirtieth Annual Conference - Grand Rapids
    - Proceedings, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 884)
    - Conference Material, 1976 (Box 74, Folder 885)
  - Thirty-first Annual Conference - Vancouver
    - Proceedings, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 886)
    - Conference Material, 1977 (Box 75, Folder 887)
  - Thirty-second Annual Conference - Latrobe, PA
    - Proceedings, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 888)
    - Conference Material, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 889)
  - Thirty-third Annual Conference - New Brighton, MN
    - Proceedings, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 890)
    - Conference Material, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 891)
  - Thirty-fourth Annual Conference - Denver
    - Proceedings, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 892)
    - Conference Material, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 893)
  - Thirty-fifth Annual Conference - St. Louis
    - Proceedings, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 894)
    - Conference Material, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 895)
  - Thirty-sixth Annual Conference - Toronto
    - Proceedings, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 896)
    - Conference Material, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 897)
    - Records of host librarian, R. Grant Bracewell, 1980-1982 (Box 125, Folder 48)
  - Thirty-seventh Annual Conference
    - Proceedings, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 898)
    - Conference Material, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 899)
  - Thirty-eighth Annual Conference - Holland, MI
    - Proceedings, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 900)
    - Conference Material, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 901)
  - Thirty-ninth Annual Conference - Madison, NJ
    - Proceedings, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 902)
    - Conference materials, 1985 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Fortieth Annual Conference - Kansas City
    - Proceedings, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 903)
    - Conference Material (Box 77, Folder 904)
  - Forty-first Annual Conference - Berkeley
    - Proceedings, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 905)
    - Conference Material, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 906)
  - Forty-second Annual Conference - Wilmore, KY
    - Proceedings, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 907)
    - Conference Material, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 908)
  - Forty-third Annual Conference - Columbus
    - Proceedings, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 909)
    - Attendee packet, 1989 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Forty-fourth Annual Conference - Evanston
    - Proceedings, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 910)
    - Conference materials, 1990 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Forty-fifth Annual Conference - Toronto
    - Proceedings, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 911)
    - Conference materials, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Exhibits, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Registrations, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Speakers, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Sponsors, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Forty-sixth Annual Conference - Dallas
    - Proceedings, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 912)
    - Conference Material, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 913)
  - Forty-seventh Annual Conference - Vancouver
    - Proceedings, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 914)
    - Conference Material, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 915)
  - Forty-eighth Annual Conference - Pittsburgh
    - Proceedings, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 916)
    - Conference Material, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 917)
  - Forty-ninth Annual Conference - Nashville
    - Proceedings, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 918)
    - Conference Material, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 919)
  - Fiftieth Annual Conference - Denver
    - Proceedings, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 920)
- Publications, Series X
  - Newsletters
    - Newsletters - copies of record
      - News Bulletin, 1948-1953 (Box 81, Folder 926-927)
      - Volumes 1-13, 1953-1966 (Box 81, Folder 928-933)
      - Volumes 14-20, 1966-1973 (Box 82, Folder 934-938)
      - Volumes 21-25 (bound volume), 1973-1978 (Box 83, Folder 939)
      - Volumes 26-35 (2 bound volumes), 1978-1988 (Box 84, Folder 940-941)
      - Volumes 36-40 (bound volume), 1988-1993 (Box 85, Folder 942)
    - Newsletters - duplicate copies
      - Volumes 1-6, 1953-1959 (Box 85, Folder 943-947)
      - Volumes 7-20, 1959-1973 (Box 86, Folder 948-952i)
      - Volumes 21-40, 1973-1993 (Box 133, Folder 1-20)
    - CAT MEWS (cataloging newsletter), 1976-1977 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Bibliography Series
    - Guide to the Study of the Holiness Movement, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 953)
    - Thomas Merton: A Bibliography, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 954)
    - Sermon on the Mount: History of Interpretation and Bibliography, 1975 (Box 87, Folder 955)
  - Monograph Series
    - Divine Imagination: William Blake's Major Prophetic Visions, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 956)
    - Social Ethics Among Southern Baptists, 1917-1969, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 957)
    - Harmonists: A Folk-Cultural Approach, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 958)
    - Pilgrimage of Faith: Legacy of the Otterbeins, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 959)
    - Perfectionist Persuasion: The Holiness Movement and American Methodism, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 960)
    - No Foot of Land: Folklore of American Methodist Itinerants, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 961)
    - Black Religions and American Evangelicalism: White Protestants Plantation Missions and the Flowering of Negro Christianity, 1975 (Box 88, Folder 962)
    - Judaism in German Christian Theology Since 1945: Christianity and Israel Considered in Terms of Mission, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 963)
    - Mystery and the Unconscious: Study on the Thought of Paul Ricoeur, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 964)
    - Salvation in the Slums: Evangelical Social Welfare Works, 1865-1920, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 965)
    - Creativity in Henry Wieman, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 966)
  - Index to Religious Periodical Literature
    - Volume 1, 1949-1952 (Box 89, Folder 967)
    - Volume 2, 1953-1954 (Box 89, Folder 968)
    - Volume 3, 1955-1956 (Box 90, Folder 969)
    - Supplement, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 970)
    - Supplement, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 971)
    - Volume 4, 1957-1959 (Box 90, Folder 972)
    - Supplement, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 973)
    - Supplement, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 974)
    - Volume 5, 1960-1962 (Box 90, Folder 975)
    - Supplement, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 976)
    - Volume 6, 1963-1964 (Box 91, Folder 977)
    - Supplement, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 978)
    - Volume 7, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 979)
    - Supplement, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 980)
    - Volume 8, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 981)
    - Supplement, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 982)
    - Volume 9, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 983)
    - Semi-Annual, 1971 Jan-Jun (Box 92, Folder 984)
    - Semi-Annual, 1971 Jul- Dec (Box 93, Folder 985)
    - Semi-Annual, 1972 Jan-Jun (Box 93, Folder 986)
    - Volume 10, 1971-1972 (Box 93, Folder 987)
    - Semi-Annual, 1973 Jan-Jun (Box 93, Folder 988)
    - Semi-Annual, 1973 Jul-Dec (Box 93, Folder 989)
    - Semi-Annual, 1974 Jan-Jun (Box 93, Folder 990)
    - Volume 11, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 991)
    - Semi-Annual, 1975 Jan-Jun (Box 94, Folder 992)
    - Semi-Annual, 1975 Jul-Dec (Box 94, Folder 993)
    - Semi-Annual, 1976 Jan-Jun (Box 94, Folder 994)
    - Volume 12, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 995)
  - Religion Index One
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1977 Jan-Jun (Box 95, Folder 996)
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1977 Jul-Dec (Box 95, Folder 997)
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1978 Jan-Jun (Box 95, Folder 998)
    - Periodical: Volume 13, 1977-1978 (Box 96, Folder 999)
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1979 Jan-Jun (Box 96, Folder 1000)
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1979 Jul-Dec (Box 96, Folder 1001)
    - Periodicals: Semi-Annual, 1980 Jan-Jun (Box 96, Folder 1002)
    - Periodicals: Volume 14, 1979-1980 (Box 97, Folder 1003)
    - Volumes 1-11, 16, 1949-1984 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Volumes 17-22, 198501990 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Religion Index Two
    - Multi-Author Works, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 1004)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 1005)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1970-1975 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1976-1980 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Multi-Author Works, 1984-1990 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Religion Indexes
    - Thesaurus, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 1006)
    - Thesaurus: First Supplement, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1007)
    - Thesaurus: Second Supplement, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 1008)
    - Thesaurus, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 1009)
    - Thesaurus, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 1010)
  - Index to Book Reviews in Religion
    - Index, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 1011-1014)
    - Supplement, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 1015)
    - Index, 1949-1959 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Index, 1960-1968 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Index, 1986, 1988 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Index, 1989, 1990 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - ATLA Technical Service Section
    - Current LC Subject Readings, 1987, 1991-1992 (Box 99, Folder 1016)
    - Newsletter, 1992 (Box 99, Folder 1017)
    - Theology Cataloging Bulletin, 1992-1994 (Box 99, Folder 1018)
    - Theological Cataloging Bulletin, 1995-1997 (Box 99, Folder 1019)
  - Research in Ministry
    - Index to Doctor of Ministry Project Reports and Theses, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 1020)
    - Index to Doctor of Ministry Project Reports and Theses, 1981-1983 (Box 100, Folder 1021)
    - Index to Doctor of Ministry Project Reports and Theses, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 1022)
    - Index to Doctor of Ministry Project Reports and Theses, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 1023)
  - Methodist Reviews Index
    - Volume 1, 1989 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - General
    - Catalogs, Program Notes (Box 100, Folder 1024)
    - Program Notes, vol. 1 no. 1 - vol. 3, no. 2, 1988-1991 (Box 125, Folder 42)
    - Essays in Celebration of the First Fifty Years, ed. by M. Patrick Graham, Valerie R. Hotchkiss, Kenneth E. Rowe, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 1025)
    - Brochure:"Be a Theological Librarian", 1961 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Scholarships, Fellowships and Grants, Series XI
  - Scholarship and Fellowship Programs
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Minutes, 1959-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1026)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Reports and Correspondence, 1958-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1027)
    - Lilly Endowment Correspondence and Financial Statements, 1962-1967 (Box 101, Folder 1028)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Application Forms and Evaluation Forms, 1959-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1029)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 101, Folder 1030)
    - Lilly Endowment Correspondence Regarding Grant Renewal, 1961-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1031)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 101, Folder 1032)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Correspondence, 1962-1969 (Box 101, Folder 1033)
    - Reports from Award Winners, 1959-1962 (Box 101, Folder 1034)
    - Foreign Seminary Librarians, 1962-1964 (Box 102, Folder 1035)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships: Publicity, 1960-1965 (Box 102, Folder 1036)
    - Commission on Lilly Endowment Scholarships and Sealantic Fellowship Program, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 1037)
    - Commission on Scholarships and Fellowships: Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1038)
    - Sealantic Fellowship Program Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 102, Folder 1039)
    - Sealantic Fellowship Program Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 102, Folder 1040)
    - Sealantic Fellowship Program: Minutes, Reports and Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 102, Folder 1041)
    - Sealantic Fellowship Program: Application Form (Box 102, Folder 1042)
  - Grant proposals
    - Proposal to the Frank E. and Seba B. Payne Foundation, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 1043)
    - Proposal to the Lilly Endowment, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 1044)
    - Planning Reports to the Lilly Endowment, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 1045)
    - Proposal to the Lilly Endowment, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 1046)
    - Proposal to the Henry Luce Foundation, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 1047)
    - Proposal to the Henry Luce Foundation, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 1048)
    - Proposal to the Henry Luce Foundation, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 1049)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 1050)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 1051)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1052)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 1053)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 1054)
    - Official Notice of Action from the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1992 (Box 103, Folder 1055)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 1056)
    - Proposal to the National Endowment for the Humanities, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 1057)
    - Proposal to the Pew Charitable Trusts, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 1058)
    - Correspondence: Pew Charitable Trusts, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 1059)
    - Proposal to the Pew Charitable Trusts, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 1060)
    - Proposal to the Pew Charitable Trusts, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 1061)
    - Correspondence: Foundations, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 1062)
- Financial Records, Series XII
  - Treasurer's Statements, 1958-1969 (Box 105, Folder 1063-1064)
  - Treasurer's Records, 1979-1983 (Box 105, Folder 1065)
  - Budget Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 105, Folder 1066)
  - Income Tax Returns, 1971-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1067)
  - Federal Tax Forms, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 1068)
  - Funding information, 1955-1959 (Box 105, Folder 1069)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1980-1983 (Box 105, Folder 1070)
  - Correspondence regarding TIAA-CREF, 1983-1984 (Box 105, Folder 1071)
  - Correspondence regarding Insurance, 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 1072)
  - Financial report, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 43)
  - Budget planning, 1986-1987 (Box 136, Folder 16)
- Oral History, Series XIII
  - Interview with Grant Bracewell, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 1073)
  - Interview with Helen Knubel, 1976-1978 (Box 106, Folder 1074)
  - Interview with Rosalyn Lewis, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 1075)
  - Interview with Eugene McLeod, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 1076)
  - Interview with Betty O'Brien, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 1077)
  - Interview with Stephen Peterson, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 1078)
  - Interview with Erich Schultz, 1995 (Box 106, Folder 1079)
  - Interview with John Trotti, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 1080-1081)
  - Interview with David Wartluft, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 1082-1083)
  - Correspondence and Paper by J. Stillson Judah, 1990-1994 (Box 107, Folder 1084)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box 107, Folder 1085)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 1086)
- Programs, Series XIV
  - Library Development Program
    See also Record Group No. 81
    - Self-Appraisal Guide, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Library Consulting
    - Consultant's Reports (By Library) (Box 108, Folder 1087-1088)
    - Biblical Seminary, CA, 1980-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1089)
    - Columbia Theological Seminary, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 1090)
    - Concordia Theological Seminary, 1981 (Box 108, Folder 1091)
    - Golden Gate Baptist Theological Seminary (Box 108, Folder 1092)
    - Lutheran Rice Seminary, 1977-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1093)
    - Mary Immaculate Seminary, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1094)
    - Methodist Theological Seminary, OH (Box 108, Folder 1095)
    - North American Baptist Seminary, 1979-1980 (Box 108, Folder 1096)
    - Orchard Lake Schools, MI, 1982 (Box 108, Folder 1097)
    - Regent College, 1978-1981 (Box 108, Folder 1098)
    - Reformed Theological Seminary, 1977 (Box 108, Folder 1099)
    - Saint Francis Seminary, 1976-1977 (Box 108, Folder 1100)
    - Theological Library Cooperation, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1111)
    - Western Evangelical Seminary, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 1112)
    - Funding (Box 108, Folder 1113)
    - Project to Index and Preserve Periodical Literature in Religion, 1991 (Box 108, Folder 1114)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 108, Folder 1115)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 109, Folder 1116)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 109, Folder 1117)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 109, Folder 1118)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 109, Folder 1119)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1972 (Box 109, Folder 1120)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 109, Folder 1121)
  - Periodical Exchange/ Library Material Exchange (after 1977)
    - Plan for Periodical Exchange and List of Periodicals to be Exchanged, 1948 (Box 109, Folder 1122)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 109, Folder 1123)
    - Reports, 1948-1977 (Box 109, Folder 1124)
    - Manual, 1954 (Box 109, Folder 1125)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1126-1128)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 109, Folder 1129)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 109, Folder 1130-1132)
    - Correspondence and List of Participants, 1963-1969 (Box 110, Folder 1133)
    - Questionnaire, 1953 (Box 110, Folder 1134)
    - Questionnaire, 1973 (Box 110, Folder 1135)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 110, Folder 1136)
    - Some Exchange Lists (Box 110, Folder 1137)
    - Form Letters and Memos (Box 110, Folder 1138)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 110, Folder 1139)
  - Monograph Preservation
    - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 110, Folder 1140)
    - Marketing Potential Institution Reports, 1987 (Box 110, Folder 1141)
  - LIBRARYNET
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 44)
    - Results from questionnaire (information about member libraries), 1987 (Box 125, Folder 45)
- Audio-Visual Materials, Series XV
  - Photographs and Slides
    - Third Annual Conference - Chicago, IL, 1949 (Box 111A, Folder 1)
    - Tenth Annual Conference - Berkeley, CA, 1956 (Box 111A, Folder 2)
    - Eleventh Annual Conference - Ft. Worth, TX, 1957 (Box 111A, Folder 3)
    - Fourteenth Annual Conference - St. Paul, MN, 1960 (Box 111A, Folder 4)
    - Fifteenth Annual Conference - Washington, DC, 1961 (Box 111A, Folder 5)
    - Seventeenth Annual Conference - Mill Valley, CA, 1963 (Box 111A, Folder 6)
    - Twentieth Annual Conference - Louisville, KY, 1966 (Box 111A, Folder 7)
    - Twenty-fourth Annual Conference - New Orleans, LA, 1970 (Box 111A, Folder 8)
    - Twenty-sixth Annual Conference - Waterloo, Ontario, 1972 (Box 111A, Folder 9)
    - Thirty-second Annual Conference - Latrobe, PA, 1978 (Box 111A, Folder 10)
    - Thirty-sixth Annual Conference - Toronto, Ontario, 1982 (Box 111A, Folder 11)
    - Forty-first Annual Conference - Berkeley, CA, 1987 (Box 111A, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous individuals associated with ATLA (Box 111A, Folder 13)
    - Oversize box containing scrapbooks documenting various theological seminaries and a box of unidentified slides, 1957 (Box 111)
  - Microfilm
    - Executive Committee minutes and conference-related, 1954-1965 (Box 112)
  - Audio Cassettes
    - Interviews, incl. with Raymond and Jean Morris, Alice Wilcox, Stephen Peterson, Betty O'Brien, David Wartluft, John Trotti (Box 113)
    - Conference, 1968 (Box 114)
    - Conference, 1969 (Box 115)
    - Conference, 1973 (Box 116)
    - Conference, 1979 (Box 117)
    - Conference, 1979 (Box 118)
    - Conference, 1980 (Box 119)
    - Conference, 1982 (Box 120)
    - Meeting, 1982 (Box 121)